Hello Hello,
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте
from Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky, where are you from?
из Украины город Хмельницкий Вы откуда Я
keeps at gunpoint,
просто я просто держит под прицелом
therefore,
поэтому
in no case
ни в коем случае
about the fact that Wait if I didn’t
о том что Подождите если бы не
support it to change, then I would
поддерживал чтобы поменялось я бы тогда
say differently. Man sees further. You are
по-другому говорю Человек видит дальше
finished Orcs tell you about it.
Вы нет Вы допускаете
could just give up no one would have died and
могли просто сдаться никто бы не умер а
you could not have attacked no one is not true but
вы могли не напасть никто неправда но
no you if you cherished the country your country
нет вы если херачили страну вашу страну
inside your country several cities
внутри вашей страны несколько городов
after the stress it is
после напряжения
very good that you started trying it That
очень хорошо что вы начали это пробовали
is, as I understand it, we
То есть я так понимаю что мы
bombed ourselves with you for 8 years and  you decided
8 лет с вами бомбили себя и вы решили
to help us bomb even more a
помочь ещё больше нас бомбить
lot of fields,
много поля
many different situations are happening, we understand the
происходит многие всякие ситуации понял
multipolarity of the modern world, it
многополярность современного мира она
is based on different centers of power, that
базируется на разных центрах силы то
is, there are centers of power America Britain
есть есть центры силы Америка Британия
China and Iran Ukraine no Ukraine is a
Китай и Иран Украина нет Украина есть
puppet of America Russia is a
марионеткой Америки Россия есть
puppet of Iran we see who
марионеткой Ирана мы видим кто
supplies weapons to Ukraine  America through
поставляет оружие Украине Америка через
other countries also yes Russia supplies
другие страны также да Россия поставляет
weapons to Iran Russia does not matter Russia is a
оружие Иран Россия неважно Россия
backward country of the Third World, it does not
отсталая страна Третьего Мира она не
produce its modern equipment, it
выпускает свое современное оборудование
got some technologies from a
ей досталось некоторые технологии от
more highly developed civilization of
более высокоразвитой цивилизации
the Soviet Yes, which gave 14 other
Советской Да которые дали 14 остальных
republics so the Soviet Union after the
республик так Советского Союза после
collapse of the USSR, Russia became a
выхода развал СССР Россия стала отстала
technological country behind  did not create
технологической страной не создала
anything qualitatively new and now
ничего качественно нового так и сейчас
no we are also in charge of
нет мы тоже смотрите нас курирует
Iran you are subordinate to Iran we are
Иран вы подчиняетесь ирану мы
subordinate to the United States of America
подчиняется соединенным штатам Америки
yes, that is, these are the poles of the world now
да то есть вот такие полюса мира сейчас
in the world community there is a consensus on the
в мировом сообществе есть консенсус о
division of the Russian Federation center of
разделении Российской Федерации центр
power China center of power Iran center of power
силы Китай центр силы Иран центр силы
Britain center  The forces of the United States of
Британии центр силы Соединенные Штаты
America will divide the Russian Federation into
Америки разделят Российскую Федерацию на
four zones of influence So China will take
четыре зоны влияния Так Китай заберет
Siberia and the Far East for itself America
себе Сибирь и Дальний Восток Америка
will take gas and on auto-containing regions
возьмет газа и на автосодержащие регионы
Britain will traditionally land in the
Британия традиционно высадится в
Arkhangelsk region
Архангельской области
Iran will receive a donut hole but
Иран получит дырочку от бублика но тоже
will also consider that it, as it were, divided the
будет считать что он как бы поделил
Russian Federation We are Ukrainians
Российскую Федерацию Мы украинцы
we will remain
останемся
vassals of America because we are not yet the
вассалами Америки потому что мы еще не
center of power What are you but
есть центром силы Какие вы вот но
Ukraine will remain the Russian Federation
Украина останется Российской Федерации
will disintegrate and Ukrainians this is where after the
распадется и украинцы вот куда после
victory of Ukraine the whole army
победы Украины денется вся эта армия
will go private military companies will be created
будут созданы частные военные компании
Yes to protect various production facilities
Да по охране разных производ объектов
in Yamal Yes, for example, in different KhMAO games
на Ямале Да например в разных ХМАО игре
in the oil-bearing regions, that is, the Ukrainians
в нефтеносных регионах то есть Украинцы
will play the role of, let's say, security
будут выполнять роль скажем так охранных
companies for the American gas
предприятий на вот американской газовой
oil production of
нефтедобычи
your former ones, for example, the Victory of Ukraine
ваших бывших допустим Победы Украины
after the collapse of the Russian Federation after
после развала Российской Федерации после
look now in the spa, why does it
смотрите сейчас в выспа почему
win you are preparing you to smoothly
же побеждает вас готовят вас плавно
cook the surrender of surrender, do you think
варят сдачи капитуляции вы думаете
why they left the type of this From
почему ушли типа из этого Из
They betrayed the Kiev region why they left
Киевской области предали почему ушли из
Kherson they betrayed why it wasn’t
Херсона предали почему это всё не
Ukraine that knocked it out True, Ukraine didn’t have
Украина выбила Правда Украины не было
so many forces That is, you have traitors Yes,
столько сил То есть у вас предатели Да
six letters traitor Putin is a traitor Yes
шесть букв предатель Путин предатель Да
They mimic the Patriots Yes
Они мимикрируют под Патриотов Да
on purpose They deliberately attacked
специально Они специально напали на
Ukraine with a small limited
Украину небольшим ограниченным
contingent could only attack immediately
контингентом могли лишь напасть сразу
pay And yes, in 3 days, but they brought a
заплатить И всё да за 3 дня но они ввели
limited contingent to
ограниченный контингент
Ukraine and NATO to grind it, then they
Украине и НАТО перемолоть его потом
mobilized mobs, they let them
мобилизировали мобиков дали им
grind And so on Russia sends
перемолоть И так дальше Россия пускает
limited waves to death and
на смерть ограниченные волны да
mobilized and so on And
мобилизированных и так далее И
contract soldiers, that is, in the same gas
контрактников то есть в том же самом газ
Tom Or left
Том Или покидали покидали ваших
they died of your paratroopers and everyone for them is
Десантников сдохли они и все за них
now Forgotten, that is, Russia, under the guise of a
теперь Забыли то есть Россия под видом
special military operation, is
специальные военной операции проводит
demilitarizing
демилитаризацию Дело в том что как
they can market anything there
могут там базарить что угодно
Who withdrew troops from the State
Кто вывел войска из ГД
Duma
р
Yes, everything that is, the fall of the Berlin Wall,
Да всё то есть падение берлинской стены
under whom it was under Gorbachev, everything is
при кем было при горбачёве тут все
absolutely ca who are you troops from the Kiev
абсолютно ца кто вы войска из Киевской
region Who withdrew troops from Kherson Who is
области Кто вывел войска из Херсона Кто
not now Putin from the Kharkov region Yes That is,
из Харьковской области не теперь Путин
you are very  cool, they made
да То есть вам очень классно сделали
such a kind of cool Well, who could
такую как бы классную Ну Кто бы мог
unfriend the Russian Federation if in
раздружить Российскую Федерацию если в
Russia they took it and started to fight to the fullest,
России взял и начал воевать на полную
no one would have come to the lamanche
никто бы так вы дошли до ламанша
dolomasha in any type and they took everything
доломаша по-любому типа и все взяли там
normal there, in short, they captured everything, but for some
нормальные короче все захватили но
reason they only let them into battle  a
почему-то в бой пускают только
limited contingent doesn’t it seem to you
ограниченный контингент вам не кажется
that Belarus is not including the type of play
это Беларусь не включая типа играют
mood Now Belarus is
настроение Вот сейчас Беларуси
not connected to Belarus
подключиться на Беларуси не включается
because this Lukashenka is also a
потому что этот Лукашенко он тоже
traitor Yes, he plays
предатель Да он играет для
such a role for the public so that
общественности такую роль для того чтобы
you don’t have consolidation, for example,
у вас не пришло консолидация например на
around Prigogine of some yes
вокруг пригожина какого-нибудь да
for example, who will now say all of us, in
например который сейчас скажет всю у нас
short, the power has betrayed us and we must
короче власть предала и мы должны короче
throw it off and win back the Ukrainians,
её скинуть и отвоевать украинцев
shooter, yes, and that’s what makes him an
стрелкового вагнеравно почему то есть
outcast.
это предательство все предательство на
was, do
Путин был
you remember from where he started this
Вы помните из чего начинал свой этот
working path, he was in the GDR in the German
рабочий путь он был в ГДР в германский
Democratic Republic,
Демократической Республике да
yes, that is, the intelligence that was there
то есть разведка которая была там очень
worked very closely with the intelligence of Western
тесно сотрудничала с разведкой западных
countries That is, when a person who
стран То есть когда человек который
was in Moscow, his contacts with
находился в Москве у него контакты с
foreign intelligence were limited
иностранными разведками были ограничены
to zero  people who were somewhere with
до нуля люди которые находились где-то
foreign intelligence services, that
иностранными разведками так и было то
is, Putin was most likely recruited back
есть Путина скорее всего завербовали еще
then, they promoted him up the stairs Well, how
тогда продвинули его по лестнице Ну как
was it just a dude who
был просто чувачок который собчаком
carried a suitcase as a Sobchak, here he was promoted to the government
носил чемодан тут его продвинули в прави
under Yeltsin, a completely pro-Western
при ельцине полностью прозападное
government, but there couldn’t
правительство же было не мог там
be a person of what kind  some
появиться человек каких-то
patriotic views, but then they
патриотических воззрений да потом его
made him there, he already became old Yes, he
сделали есть уже стал старенький Да он
became uncontrolled by the West, and they made
Неуправляемый западом стал да сделали
an operation, a successor, and
операцию преемник и
this one
этот и
made Putin president  of the
сделали Путина президента Почему
Asian region and therefore, with
азиатского региона и поэтому руками
Putin’s hands, for 2 they made a type of Chechen war
Путина за 2 сделали типа Чеченскую войну
and crushed the Chechnya of
и задавили Чечню
America, it turns out that is, a bunch of
Америки получается то есть куча
Russian soldiers put
российских солдат положили тогда
Pskov Paratroopers then. Do you remember what
Псковские Десантников Вы же помните что
happened to them?
с ними было Да
we went there as long as we
И так и боевики потом ушли туда сколько
put the storming of Grozny on New Year's Eve
положили штурм Грозного в Новогоднюю
If you
Если мы с вами
and Lebed are the swan general You had what they
и Лебедь генерал-лебедь У вас был что с
did to him killed him killed and he did
ним сделали убили его убили а он
the right things from the point of view of the Russians
правильные вещи с точки зрения россиян
like he said so he was taken under the
типа он говорил так так его взяли под
supervision of the Russian special services which are
надзором спецслужб российских которые
completely controlled
Полностью подконтрольные
by us  we see that it’s completely in the Russian
мы видим что полностью в Российской
Federation Well, how could you
Федерации Ну как бы вы можете там
want it there, don’t want it, I can want it, we are
хотеть этого не хотеть я могу хотеть мы
small pawns in this game, we
маленькие пешки в этой игре мы просто
can just quarrel here, my team will
можем тут ссориться там моя команда
win, your team will win Big
выиграет ваша команда выиграть Большие
uncles play on this chessboard,
дяди играют на этой шахматной доске
they play by countries and not from us  depends on your
играют странами и не от нас зависит
own figures You understand, we are
самостоятельно фигуры Вы же понимаете мы
talking
говорим
normally
нормально
You, for example, once saw where
Вы например видели когда-то где живут
Putin’s daughters live Of course not even pictures
дочки Путина Конечно нет даже фотки
definitely
определенно
Putin is at war with the whole world
Путин ведет войну со всей миром
They are the most vulnerable can capture there
Они самые уязвимые могут захватить там
you were here Imagine Comrade Stalin And
вы были вот Представьте товарищ Сталин А
his son has
сын у него
property there But this  it would be a little
имущество там Но это было бы немножко
or in baden-baden
или в баден-бадене
it was a little And if we look at the
это было немножко А если мы посмотрим
entire guide of Peskov where the children daughter
все руководство Песков где дети дочка
studied in France, respectively,
училась во Франции соответственно
Peskov was the son of Peskov, he was at the
Песков был сын Пескова был на фронте же
artillery front, the son of sand
артиллерии сын песком
I think that these are all tales of the type in order
Я думаю что это все байки типа для того
to show And so on  Yes, they
чтобы показали И так дальше Да вот у них
all have them, yes Children, Peskov’s daughter studied
у всех да Дети вот дочка Пескова училась
in France, yes, she had an
во Франции да было при
internship there at the Council of Europe,
Совете Европы там стажировку проходила
that is,
то есть
in fact, it even makes sense to discuss it,
на самом деле даже смысле это обсуждать
give examples, even there, at least
приводить примеры даже там как минимум
take Shoigu’s daughter with her boyfriend,
взять дочку Шойгу с её парнем
this is generally a
это вообще
disgrace,
позорище
the Minister of Defense and you  you write there some
министр обороны и ты пишешь там какой-то
you go shorter like in Dubai take a picture
ты едешь короче типа в Дубае фоткаешься
there look how we chill exhale
Там смотрите как мы чилим выдохните
now [ __ ] with me if in fact in a
сейчас [__] со мной если по факту
good way I would go there
по-хорошему взял бы поехал туда
somehow supported
как-то поддержал
this operation
этот операцию
to him There they wrote like you can collect the
ему Там писали типа можешь собрать там
boys there to help go to  you are all
пацанам на помощь пошли в жопу вы все
patriots no Well,
патриоты нет
yes, yes, now, well, it’s
Ну да да сейчас ну
hard to determine what, in this
сложно вообще определить что в этом
regard, it’s definitely, that is, well, it’s
плане сказать это определенно то есть ну
always been like this with us because she’s
это всегда у нас так было потому что она
always the stress of her entire
всегда все время напряжение всего ее
existence of the Russian Federation itself.
существования самой Российской Федерации
It has always collapsed and nothing special, that
Она всегда развалилась и ничего особо то
is  let's say
есть никакого вот допустим русского
there was no goal for the Russian people, there
народа никакой цели не было никакой все
was no goal, everyone worked like this, they went here there was no
работали вот так ходили сюда не было
goal, let's say you started it there,
цель допустим вот у вас она началась там
work with the population began there  let's say
работа с населением началось там 12 13 4
one look after another
нас у одного взгляда допустим за другой
against the other does not know at all then there
против другой вообще не знает тогда
is no such association of some kind
здесь нет такого объединения какого-то
Why do you have monarchists for the tsar there
Почему у вас там есть монархисты за царя
who are communists they are like there for the
есть которые коммунисты они типа там за
Soviet Union against the public it
Советский Союз против там общественный
turns out Well, it’s generally incomprehensible and Russia,
получается Ну вообще непонятно и Россия
if we look, we’ll take Ukraine
вот если мы посмотрим возьмём Украина
Ukraine has only been increasing in recent years
Украина последние лет только
Yes, it was the UNR then they
увеличивается Да вот она УНР было потом
stopped, nothing annexed
перестали не стали ничего присоединил
the territory, it’s more yes, like,
территории настало больше да типа
and Russia is just falling apart in 917,
и Россия только распадается 917 году был
the first collapse of the Russian Empire
первый распад Российской империи
separated Finland Poland Ukraine still
отделились Финляндия Польша Украина еще
a lot of territories, then Lenin reassembled a little part So to make the Soviet
немножко часть Так сделать Советский
Union, that is  The Russian Empire 20 in
Союз то есть Российская империя 20 в 91
91, it crumbled, already separated 14
году она рассыпалась уже отделилась 14
republics and now there is a period of
республик и сейчас идет период
preparation for the collapse of the Russian Federation,
подготовки распада Российской Федерации
that’s why you give these republics
на вот зачем у вас этим республикам дают
subjectivity, yes they have their own heads of
субъектность да у них там свои главы
republics there, their Constitutions Yes,
республик свои Конституции Да
if we look at Yakutia under Lenin,
если мы посмотрим Якутия при Ленине
Lenin what did the communists settled
Ленин что сделал коммунисты заселяли
Russians and Ukrainians resettled Yakutia in this way
Якутию русскими и украинцами вот так
so that the share of the
переселяли туда для того чтобы долю
ethnic population of the Irkutsk Sokh
этнического населения Иркутского Соха
would be reduced by 91, when the Russian
уменьшат к 91 году когда Российская
Soviet Union collapsed, the Yakuts were
Советский Союз распался якутов было
less than half
меньше половины
less, there were something like 20 or 30
меньше было их что-то было там 20 или 30
percent now as a result of
процентов сейчас уже в результате
activities in independent Russia from  -due to
деятельности в независимой России из-за
the outflow of the Russian population from Yakutia
оттока русского населения из Якутии
due to internal pressure Yes
из-за внутреннего давления Да
Revival to start a language there Impose
Возрождение там начинать язык Навязывать
again on Yakutsk signs in the Yakut language
снова Якутске вывески на якутском языке
for sugar there is an outflow of the Russian
на сахар идет отток российского
population and now more than 50 percent
населения и сейчас более 50 процентов
of it is already ethnic sugar, that is, this
там уже этнический сахар то есть уже эту
territory is already being prepared for
территорию готовят к обретению
independence in Tatarstan  I think it’s not for
Независимости в Татарстане Я думаю не
you to tell what the mood is, they
вам рассказывать какие там настроение
actually discussed with friends
на самом деле обсуждали с друзьями о том
that we often ask for our telegram channels,
что часто просим наши телеграм-каналы
public Z, and so on.
паблики Z и так далее То есть популярная
some migrant did something somewhere, that's
какое-то мигрант что-то где-то сделал
how bad it was, there were no words
вот как плохо именно не было вообще слов
at all, in fact, all the time that this was mine, it
вообще-то всё время что вот мой вот это
was
определенному случаи бывают очевидно по
all there.  this,
всей большой стране Но это
respectively, could not be posted But
соответственно можно было не постить Но
this is sure to be posted in huge
это обязательно постят в огромных
channels this ad starts I
каналах это реклама начинается я
monitor your channel is called
мониторю ваш канал называется
multinational There they pick up everything there they
многонационал Там они подбирают все там
drive on migrants migrants
гонят на мигрантами мигранты там что-то
raped something there migrants stole migrants
изнасиловали мигранты украли мигранты
such that is, Russians seem to
такие то есть русские вроде как не
do nothing wrong everything  they make a bad
делают ничего плохого всё делают плохой
immigrant, it inflates, yes, there are also
иммигрант это раздувает да также есть
all sorts of channels there, they
там всякие тоже каналы они вот там
are there Bulba of Thrones, we have
Бульба престолов такой есть у нас
some kind of anonymous channel Yes, he
какой-то анонимный канал Да вот он
knows this channel, damn And you What
знаете этот канал [__] А вы Какие
channels are you watching, I
каналы смотрите
just see that Well, in many it’s the same,
просто вижу что Ну во многих одинаково
everything is the same completely
всё одинаковое полностью
it starts  disperse like uh
такое начинает разгонять типа э-э вот
this anti-migrant topic plus look in
эту антимигрантскую тему плюс смотрите в
Russia yes uh foreigners uh last
России да э иностранцам э-э в прошлом
year in the twenty-second year they issued
году в двадцать втором году выдали
passports to 180 or 100 with something thousand
паспорта 180 или 100 с чем-то тысяч
Tajik citizens of Tajikistan not Russians
таджиков гражда Таджикистана не русским
from the DPR who kind of added
из ДНР который вроде как присоединили
passports and then  until now, they didn’t really give out to
паспорта и то до сих пор не по выдавали
everyone Yes, new territories
толком всем Да новые территории
were annexed, such as the Zaporozhye
присоединили типа там Запорожской
region, they don’t issue passports there, and
области что-то не выдают паспорта а
Tajiks are imported in
таджиков завозят
a second, I’ll tell you one case I have a
секунду расскажу один случай меня есть
friend of my friend’s wife She is already 28 years old,
подруга моего друга жена Ей уже 28 лет
they arrived When her family moved to us
они приехали Когда нам ее семья
now the region back when  she
переехала сейчас области еще когда она
was small a long time ago, that is, 25 years
маленькая была еще давно то есть 25 лет
ago, she still can’t get your passport,
назад она до сих пор не Ваш паспорт
I read your channel, I’ll reduce it in Russia, I don’t
я читаю ваши канал я снижу в России не
know these Russian nationalists there, they are
знаю эти русские там националисты они
all indignant Why can’t the Russian people from the
все возмущаются Почему русским людям из
DPR who came here,
ДНР которые приехали сюда они не могут
that’s how you get
вот как вы получить
they give out as a migrant as a guest worker because it is an
мигрантом гастарбайтером выдают потому
oligarch that is profitable, like
что это олигарха выгодно типа их
legalizing them is a labor force and there is
легализировать это рабочая сила и есть
such a Russian nationalists there already
такое там русский националисты уже там
crying that Moscow and St. Petersburg are no longer a
плачут что Москва и Питер это уже не
Russian city because there are a lot of
русский город потому что там очень много
these migrants who went from internal
вот этих мигрантов поехал из внутренней
Russian migrants there from the Caucasus
российских мигрантов там с Кавказа
external there with a strange one I
например из внешней там со странной не
won’t say what they call them There is
буду говорить как они их называют
hatred for people from Asia
Ненависть к людям из Азии есть
I think you will agree It also seems to me
Я думаю вы согласитесь Также мне кажется
like As in all countries as well as in the
как Как и во всех странах также как и в
USA certain you there also
США определенный ты там также к
refers to African Americans also
относится к афроамериканцам также
in
в
America there are yes there are states  which are
Америке есть Да есть штаты которые там
more Russian there are definitely these
более российские есть однозначно вот эти
Southern states but the American system
Южные штаты но американская система
someone their president was
кого-то у них президент был
an African American You can imagine
афроамериканец Вы можете представить
Kadyrov as president if Kadyrov
президентом Кадырова если Кадыров будет
runs for president How
баллотироваться на пост Президента Как
will the Russians react
будут русские реагировать
[ __ ] the phone turned on I think
бля телефон включился Я думаю
out I think not quite positive
вон Я думаю не совсем положительно
of course
конечно
Russia  look in Russia, inter-ethnic inter-religious conflicts are brewing,
Россия смотрите в России назревает
for example, for some reason, look here in
например почему-то смотри вот в
Bashkortostan in Ufa and Ufa, the city where the
Башкортостане в Уфе да Уфа город где
historical Tatars lived there, the
исторический там жили там татары
Bashkorts
башкорты
are building on Ancient on the site where the
строят на Древнем на месте где был
ancient Bashkordian city was Yes, it is building
древний башкордский город Да строит
there The Russian Orthodox Church
именно там Русская православная церковь
is making a temple there specially for the authorities of the
там делает храм специально власти
Republic  which Bashkortostan
Республики которые Башкортостан
sanctioned, that is, the
санкционировали то есть специально
authorities of the Muslim region specifically
власти мусульманского региона специально
sanctioned the construction of this temple
санкционировали построение этого храма
in order to create a conflict in Moscow,
для того чтобы сделать конфликт в Москве
remember on Belozero it was also
помните на белозере было тоже
that a mosque that they wanted to build a mosque
что мечеть что мечеть хотели построить
on some place where this is for
на каком-то там месте где вот это для
Christians There they say something that  for
христиан Там они что-то говорят что для
them, the Holy
них Святой
Muslim region is specially building
мусульманском регионе специально строят
us, if the Bashkord church is the
нас свя если башкордов церковь самую
largest And here, like a mosque in Moscow, yes, that
большую А тут типа мечеть в Москве да то
is, Russia before the power of Russia, well, the
есть Россию до власть России так Ну тот
same Putin Shoigu Gerasim, all these
же Путин Шойгу Герасима все эти
nabiullin And so on they are preparing for a
набиуллин И так дальше они готовят к
social explosion, an inter-ethnic and
социальному взрыву межэтническому и
inter-religious explosion, then  it’s a
межрелигиозному взрыву то есть это
matter of time and the war in Ukraine is
вопрос времени и война в Украине она
heating up this process, that is,
подогревает этот процесс то есть
there is a catalyst, for example, problems
катализатором есть например проблемы
that could last for decades.
которые могли длиться десятилетиями
Now they are starting to surface.
Сейчас они начинают всплывать наружу
someone in Russia a
министра если человек кто-то в России
year ago said that the catalog
год назад такое сказал каталожку
was thrown out the truth
закинули правда
Why isn’t everything done so simply,
Почему так не просто все делается
of course, the most important thing. It seems to
конечно тоже самое важное Мне кажется
many people that his motives are clear that he
мотивы его многим людям понятно что он
wants to go wherever he wants,
хочет вообще куда он хочет
and perhaps there are also a lot of people who
и возможно там тоже много кто что
say what And after our president I watch a
говорит А после нашего президента смотрю
speech  I don’t understand a word at all,
выступление не понимаю вообще ни слова
we
мы сегодня
said today he was some kind of nonsense or there that he
говорили он какие-то бред или там что он
will tell something necessary, he died, he
расскажет что-то нужный умер он
will tell that 53 it was shot down, he
расскажет что 53 это сбила он
tells me, I
рассказывает
don’t know where he is. Perhaps
я не знаю где он Возможно
the goals of the special operation have already been achieved
цели спецоперации уже достигнуты потому
because Ukraine no longer has Soviet weapons
что советского оружия уже у Украины нет
like  all dementalization has come now there
типа всё дементализация пришла теперь
is another weapon
есть другая оружие
it needs disarmament it means but it so
это нужно разоружение обозначает а так
happened that they came to destroy but in
получилось что пришли разрушать а в
the end
итоге
you don’t want to touch the Russians So what is
не хочется русских потрогать Так в чем
the inventory more and more of them now
инвентаризации все больше и больше они
wait wait it will begin Well, as
вот подождите подождите начнется Ну как
if I were, say, a Russian, I
бы если бы я скажем был россиянин я не
could not explain  how so Why why has
мог объяснить как так Почему почему
n’t a nuclear strike been launched so far,
ядерный удар не нанесли до сих пор
also there, that is, Russia, the city of nuclear
тоже там то есть Россия город ядерная
Dina, a power like All She, if Russia
Дина держава типа Все Она если Россия
considers the Kherson Zaporizhia region to be its own,
считает херсонскую запорожскую область
then you think it is
своими все тогда вы считаете она до сих
still so many say we have
пор так многие говорят у нас есть
nuclear weapons So what is it  it makes sense
ядерное оружие Так какой в нем смысл
if she doesn’t even hold back anything no one is
если она даже не сдерживает ничего никто
afraid they all understand perfectly well
не боится они все все прекрасно понимают
that nothing will happen In what even he’s
что ничего не будет В каком даже он
cool In what condition he is there if
прикольно В каком он там состоянии если
I see It’s just that I heard the army myself I bought
я вижу Просто я сам слышал армии Я купил
a contract Before I see let’s say how
контракт Раньше я вижу допустим как
our shells were stored let’s say for
хранились снаряды наш допустим для
artillery, that is, we were in these
артиллерии то есть мы были на этих
warehouses, it’s just, that is, they were in
складах это просто то есть лежат в
a box, it
коробке
was necessary.  it’s
нужно было Если очковал думаешь очень
funny, but now we’re not
прикол но сейчас это ничему мы не
surprised at anything, that is, we see if that
удивляемся так то есть мы видим если тот
bakhmut is how they showed you that it seems
бахмут вот как Вам показали что вроде
like they took bakhmut, but for some reason
как взяли бахмут но до сих пор почему-то
not a single official has come to bakhmud yet,
не один чиновник не приехал в бахмуд
if it’s been taken if they were still there
правда если он взят если там были до сих
already  but they don’t go Yes, here it’s like
пор уже но не идут Да тут у нас как если
ours Announce we took Kherson Zelensky
наши Объявлять мы взяли Херсон Зеленский
stopped by took a picture Yes, talked to people
заехал пофотографировался Да с людьми
said they beat off the raisins stopped by
пообщался сказали отбили изюм заехали
took pictures Yes, and here it’s been like a
пофотографировались Да а тут уже вроде
month or what they say that they kind of
месяц или что там говорят что вроде
took bahmud But nothing means
взяли бахмуд А ничего нет значит
don’t look, for example When it was here  in the
не смотри например Когда было вот на
Kharkiv region when I was swimming.
Харьковской области когда была купаться
You went there. Representatives of this
У вас ездили Там представители это
State Duma were here to imagine there are a lot of
Госдумы были вот представить там много
pictures there. Russia is here forever and that’s it.
есть фоткались Россия здесь навсегда и
some kind of one and a half
километров а тут за какой-то там полторы
or a week already How many villages recaptured over an
или неделю уже Сколько сел отбил по
area more than bakhmut in a week
площади больше чем бахмут за неделю
without huge information I try
без огромных информацию я стараюсь
just because of a year since it has been going on for
просто из-за год так как идет уже этом
more than a year already all this is going on, that is,
больше года уже все это идет то есть я
at first I was subscribed to all of the channel by
сначала на все все канал был подписан
everyone  countries immediately, that is, European
всех стран сразу то есть европейские
Ukrainian ones, so then I unsubscribed,
украинские так потом отписался
respectively, it’s better to read well, you
соответственно лучше хорошо читать
have to do it automatically.  I
приходится автоматически занимаешься Это
understand when people from
Я просто не понимаю Я когда людей из
Russia are asked if you will support a
России спрашивают поддержите ли вы
special operation, so if
спецоперацию так вот если поддерживает
you do, well, they think that they will win there, everything is
Ну они думают что они там выиграют все
fine, but if you understand something
хорошо но если ты вот понимаешь
from this special operation, why do you
с этой спецоперации что-то тут Зачем ты
support
поддерживаешь
a cave that happened to sit on a chair from a
пещера который там бывался на стул со
chair to a chair  and so on I
стула на стул присаживался и так далее В
was sitting in shorts, I can be defined That
шортах сидел я могу определён То есть
is, at least for the fighters, it’s simple and all
это как минимум за бойцов просто и все
for the fact that the fighters themselves,
за того что бойцы сами по себе
from the fact that we understand the fighters, for some reason
из того что мы понимаем бойцов почему-то
throw them to death in limited
кидает на смерть ограниченными
contingents, so that is, the longer
контингентами так то есть Чем дольше
the special operation takes, the longer they
идет спецоперация тем дольше их
recycles it turns out and then once they
утилизирует получается а потом раз
published the whole Kharkiv region because
издали целую харьковскую область потому
I will stop, that is, support them,
что я перестану то есть поддерживать их
that is, nothing will change from this.
То есть это от этого ничего не
Also, everyone will throw and they will
поменяется Также будут все кидать и меня
throw me, and so on.
кинут и так далее Все
you’re throwing yourself
типа А в чём прикол что вы нас кидаете
to death quietly quietly You
на смерть потихонечку потихонечку
understand by
Сами понимаете
Russian people It’s
русскими людьми
just that many, not many, some part
Просто многие не многие какая-то часть
of them don’t even know what demitalization is
они даже не знаю что такое демитализация
What goals Yes, to [ __ ] take over
Какие цели Да [__] захватить страну
your country, such a
вашего такая
Victory is something like when Kiev is taken or
Победа это что типа когда Киев взять или
that a
что
very clear criterion for exit at the border of
очень четкий критерий выход на границе
91 years is all  of retaking their territories,
91 года все отвоевания своих территорий
every Ukrainian has it clearly that there
у каждого украинца есть это четко что
are
есть Победы
90 percent Victories In Russia, what is
90 процентов В России что есть
not at all clear,
вообще не понятно
we laughed like that it is possible to declare
у нас смеялись типа что можно объявить
that the purpose of the special operation was this
что целью спецоперации был енот этот
Kherson raccoon and finish the special operation
Херсонский все и закончить спецоперацию
this blogger constantly spoke like
этот блогер говорил постоянно как у
mice You are also a blogger Yes  I’m a blogger Yes, well,
мышек Вы тоже блогер Да я блогер Да ну
there’s something in your back showing the light with
там что-то у вас сзади показывал светил
my channel
моим каналом
someone was sitting behind the Russian flag then he
кто-то сзади сидел Российский флаг потом
wanted to troll me for a wheelbarrow then
за тачку хотел меня затролить потом
he showed there Stream or mine or yours The
показывал там Стрим или мой или ваш
three of us ask the discord decided to go into the
Мы втроем просим дискорде решили зайти в
chat roulette
чат рулетку
on the channel
на канал
I record a lot I  I won’t get anywhere
много записываю Я же не попаду никуда
now on the stream, and on the stream there are 80
сейчас на стриме а на стриме 80
subscribers, I
подписчиков
understand that you’re just telling
это к понял то что вы просто рассказываю
for
для
a lot of things to tell, I’m just high for you
много чего рассказать я для вас я просто
when people understand, we
кайфую когда люди понимают мы нормально
talked normally, there are already people starting to
пообщались уже есть люди начинают орать
yell, I don’t like him like that
бывать его такое не люблю
Many I also track  respectively,
Многие я отслеживаю также соответственно
Prigogine and
пригожина и
Strelkov, that is, I think that they are not
Стрелкова то есть считаю что ничего не
writing anything else about some, let’s say, a situation
пишет еще о каких-то допустим ситуация
that can generally happen in general. It’s clear
что может вообще в целом произойти
that it’s
Понятное дело что это сейчас поверить
quite difficult to believe now that how it will all
довольно сложно что как это все будет
happen, but let’s say a year ago we
происходить но и допустим год назад мы
couldn’t assume that now  there will be
не могли допустим что сейчас уже будет
such a time, I’ll say a year ago it was impossible
такое время я еще скажу год назад нельзя
Prigozhin will try with
было Пригожин будет стараться со
rifle shooters with kadyr Kadyrov with
стрелковым стрелков с кадыром Кадыров с
Prigozhin That is, you have some kind of different
Пригожин То есть у вас какие-то разные
centers of power and you don’t expel all your friend,
центры сил получается и не все друг
that is, the main thing is that the very
выгони то есть главное что самая
problem is that, let’s say you
проблема в том что допустим у вас
probably  everything is happening the same way, but it’s
вероятно все так тоже происходит но это
all happening, that is, well, not to the public.
все происходит то есть ну не на публику
And with us, this is all that happens, everything is like
А у нас это все что происходит все как
correspondence, everyone who conveyed what to whom
переписки все кто кому что передал на
ran into this all, that is, it’s happening, it’s
кого наехал это все то есть происходит
being discussed by a lot of millions, what’s the matter with us,
обсуждается намного миллиона у нас в чем
what’s the difference between us  we have
дело В чем у нас разница у нас
one military center of power That is, we
военный центр силы один То есть у нас
don’t have one. For example, you have Akhmat, he’s stupid. In short, some kind of
нету Например у вас Ахмат он тупо Короче
like Kadyrov’s private army, a private army
какой-то как частная армия Кадырова
is a prigozhin.  the
нету например есть Вертикаль
defense of
Министерство обороны
others, it’s as if there are no military
других как бы нет каких-то военных
units of the probability, the
подразделения вероятности
company delivered an Ultimatum alive
компания поставили живым Ультиматум
so that they sign contracts with the
чтобы они подписали контракты с армии
Russian army, and no one wants to do this
России а этого делать Никто не хочет
because many understand, well, or there
потому что многие понимают ну или там
were something that they would illegally put Yes, and
были то что незаконно поставят Да вот и
that is already some kind of  something Ultimatum
то есть уже какой-то какие-то Ультиматум
and so on Everything begins Of course I'm waiting
и так далее Все начинается Конечно я жду
This is July 1st because until July 1st all
Вот это 1 июля потому что до 1 июля все
these crappy bastards So to speak, so that they
эти алячье выкашники Так сказать чтобы
don't sign this contract The Ministry of
не подписали этот контракт Министерство
Defense That is, they are being transferred by subordination,
обороны То есть их переводит подчинение
it's already publicly sort of like Akhmat
это уже публично вроде как Ахмат
signed And that something  there he also signed it
подписал И что что-то там еще подписала
goes with hostility and now it will be the first of July
идёт в штыки и сейчас будет первая июля
Yes, and in fact, uh, the prigozhina will, I think,
Да и по сути э-э пригожина будут я думаю
press Or either legally he may
нажимать Или либо юридически он может
have such somewhere, I read that he may
есть такая где-то я читал что он может
possibly come out of there altogether and go,
возможно выйдет вообще оттуда и поедет
well, that is, he, as it were  here they will give you. In short,
ну то есть ему как бы вот дадут Короче
you didn’t open your mouth here and there,
ты тут не рот не открывал и там э
deal with these with aboriginal
занимайся с этими с аборигенными там
diamonds there, they have shorter diamonds and so on.
алмазы у них короче и так далее
Well, let's run away. Thank you
Хорошо давайте побегу Спасибо
like this
вот так